Guide to the Papers of Mordecai Sheftall (1735-1797), undated, 1761-1867, 1873, 1932, 1941 (bulk 1777-1778) *P-12
American Jewish Historical Society, Newton Centre, MA and New York, NY
- Subgroup II: American Revolutionary and Continental Troop Commissarial Work and Provision Return Records, undated, 1777-1779, 1782-1783
  - Series II: Commissarial Records - Army, undated, 1777-1778
    - Subseries IV: Provision Returns for the 4th Regiment and 4th Battalion, undated, 1790, 1797
      - (Binder 7)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Celeron Brossard for Celeron Brossard, 00/29/1778-0/30/1778 (Item 32)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by [Illegible] for One Sergeant and Six Privates in Capt. [Seniors] Company Under the Command of John Bard Stationed at McLeland's Plantation, 01/10/1778 (Item 33)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Patrick Fitzpatrick and John White to Jesse [Senior?], 01/14/1778-04/16/1778 (Item 34)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Henry Phillips, John White, and Christopher Hillary to Jesse [Senior?] (Two Returns), 01/14/1778 (Item 35)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Henry Phillips and John White to Henry Phillips, [James] Brown, [Bernard] Patty, and Sutler Copeland, 01/14/1778-03/15/1778; Indexed #007 (Item 36)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Henry Phillips for Rations Received of Sheftall Sheftall for Henry Phillips, Lt. Fitzpatrick and Lt. Patty, 01/15/1778-03/17/1778 (Item 37)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White and Henry Phillips to Jas. Aitken [Chaplain], 01/19/1778-01/25/1778; WPA_E-0236; Indexed #013 (Item 38)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White, Henry Phillips, and Christopher Hillary with List of Numbers in Captain's Companies Provided for, 02/13/1778-02/19/1778 (Item 39)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Henry Phillips Received of Sheftall Sheftall for Rations Under the Command of Col. White, 02/13/1778-03/14/1778 (Item 40)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Christopher Hillary Received of Sheftall Sheftall Rations for Officers, 02/13/1778-02/19/1778 (Item 41)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Regiment Signed by Henry Phillips and John White to John DuCoin, 02/14/1778-02/24/1778 (Item 42)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Henry Phillips to Lt. [Thomas] Washington, 02/15/1778-03/15/1778 (Item 43)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Henry Phillips Received of Sheftall Sheftall Rations for Men, Women, and Children, 02/15/1778-03/13/1778 (Item 44)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Henry Phillips (Two Returns), 02/16/1778-02/17/1778 (Item 45)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Christopher Hillary Received of Sheftall Sheftall One Pound of Candles, 02/17/1778 (Item 46)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Christopher Hillary for Officers Rations and List of Officers, 02/20/1778-02/26/1778 (Item 47)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Henry Phillips for Lt. DuCoin, 02/22/1778-03/15/1778 (Item 48)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Henry Phillips and John White to William Routledge from 12/15/1777-02/15/1778, 02/23/1778 (Item 49)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Henry Phillips and John White for Eight Men from 12/15/1777-02/23/1778 (Item 50)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Arthur Hayes and Henry Phillips for Seven Men for Five Days "as they are going upon an expedition after Deserters", 02/24/1778; WPA_E-0249; Indexed #075 (Item 51)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Christopher Hillary for Eleven Men, 02/24/1778-03/03/1778 (Item 52)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Christopher Hillary Received from James Farquharson, for Capt. [Days], Bapt Melven, Lt. [McKenna], Ensign [Carswell], and Devalisle, 02/27/1778-03/05/1778 (Item 53)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Christopher Hillary to Walter Dixon, 02/27/1778-04/03/1778 (Item 54)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White with List of Officers and Numbers of Persons Provided for, 02/27/1778-03/05/1778 (Item 55)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White and Christopher Hillary with List of Officers and Numbers of Persons Provided for, 02/27/1778-03/05/1778 (Item 56)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Henry Phillips, 03/01/[1778]-04/15/[1778] (Item 57)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Henry Phillips and Shadrack Wright to Andrew Templeton (Two Returns), 03/01/1778-05/18-01/1778 (Item 58)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Christopher Hillary for Eleven Men, 03/03/1778-03/05/1778 (Item 59)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Christopher Hillary for the "use of a detachment… stationed at Tybee Island", 03/06/1778 (Item 60)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White with List of Officers and Numbers of Persons Provided For, 03/06/1778-03/12/1778 (Item 61)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Christopher Hillary for One Sergeant and Two Privates, 03/13/1778-03/16/1778 (Item 62)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by William Routledge for a Detachment at Tybee Island of Two Subalterns, Two Sergeants, Two Corporals, Seventeen Privates and One Woman, 03/13/1778-03/19/1778 (Item 63)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White with List of Officers and Numbers of Persons Provided For, 03/13/1778-03/19/1778 (Item 64)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White to John White from 12/15/1777-03/12/1778, 03/14/1778 (Item 65)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Henry Phillips for Soap, 03/14/1778 (Item 66)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Christopher Hillary Received of James Farquharson, 03/14/1778 (Item 67)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Henry Phillips for Col. White and Henry Phillips, 03/14/1778-04/17/1778 (Item 68)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White and George Eastmad to John DuCoin, 03/16/1778-05/06/1778 (Item 69)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by [Illegible], 03/17/1778 (Item 70)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed By George Young for Twenty-Three Men and Two Women, 03/19/1778 (Item 71)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Sheftall Sheftall Certifying That Men and Officers Belonging to the 4th Battalion on Tybee Island Under Capt. George Young of the First Company of Continental Artillery Are Due Rations of Soap and Candles, 03/19/1778; WPA_E-0265; Indexed #032 (Item 72)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John Bennis with with List of Officers and Numbers of Persons Provided For, 03/20/1778-03/26/1778 (Item 73)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Henry Phillips to Ensign Despelthiere from 12/15/1777-[02]/15/1778, 03/25/1778 (Item 74)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by [Illegible] for Twenty-five Men, 03/27/1778 (Item 75)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White with List of Officers and Numbers of Persons Provided For, 03/29/1778-04/02/1778 (Item 76)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Henry Phillips [Fragment], 03/31/[1778] (Item 77)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Sheftall Sheftall to Arthur Hayes for Rations Due, 04/[?]/1778 (Item 78)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Henry Phillips to Capt. Brossard, 04/01/1778-07/31/1778 (Item 79)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Chris Hillary, Thomas Washington, Patrick Fitzpatrick to James [?], 04/01/1778-06/01/1778 (Item 80)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White and Christopher Hillary with List of Officers and Numbers of Persons Provided for, 04/03/1778-04/09/1778 (Item 81)
        - Provision Returns for the 4th Battalion Signed by Christopher Hillary and John White (4 returns), 04/03/1778-07/31/1778 (Item 82)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion for Men, Women and Children, 04/07/1778 (Item 83)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Unsigned with List of Named Men, Women, and Children Provided for Under the Command of John White, 04/08/1778 (Item 84)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by James Brown for Men Mending Bridges for One Subaltern, Ten Privates, and Four Pioneers, 04/13/1778 (Item 85)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Henry Phillips to [Benjamin] Tetard, 04/15/1778 (Item 86)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Chris Hillary and John White to Benjamin Tetard, 04/15/1778-08/31/1778 (Item 87)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Chris Hillary and John White to [Illegible], 04/16/1778-07/31/1778 (Item 88)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Chris Hillary and John White for Augustin David Despelthiere and Romand DeLisle, 04/16/1778-07/31/1778 (Item 89)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by [Illegible] for Seventeen Men, Women, and Children, 04/18/1778 (Item 90)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion with List of Men, Women, and Children, 04/19/1778 (Item 91)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion for Fifteen Men, Women, and Children, 04/20/1778 (Item 92)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by [Illegible], 04/21?/78 (Item 93)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John Bennis for Three Men Commanded by John White, 04/21/1778 (Item 94)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by [Illegible] for Men, Women, and Children, 04/22/1778 (Item 95)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John Caswell for Rations to Lt. Caswell, 04/23/1778-05/12/1778 (Item 96)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John Bennis with Named List of Men, Women, and Children, 04/24/1778 (Item 97)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by James Stedman for Seventy-five Men, Women, and Children, 04/27/1778 (Item 98)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John Bennis for Part Rations for Going to the [South ward?], 04/28/1778 (Item 99)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John Bennis for Thirty-nine People "going out to the Southward", 04/28/1778 (Item 100)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John Bennis and Joseph Jones with a List of Persons Provided For, 04/28/1778 (Item 101)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright with List and Numbers of Captain's Companies Provided for, 05/01/1778 (Item 102)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White, for Sergeant Gold [Gould], 05/02/1778 (Item 103)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Thomas Washington for Thomas Washington, 05/05/1778 (Item 104)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White, and Shadrack Wright for Sergeant Gold [Gould], 05/05/1778 (Item 105)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Regiment Signed by John Ducoin to John Ducoin, 05/06/1778-03/31/1778 (Item 106)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright with Named List of Names of Those Provided for, 05/08/1778 (Item 107)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Joseph Day for the Bearer to Have Day's Three Rations and One for the Bearer Every Day Until Countermanded by Day's Order, 05/12/1778 (Item 108)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright with List of Soldiers Provided for, 05/14/1778 (Item 109)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright and John Caswell with Numbers of Persons Provided for, 05/15/[1778] (Item 110)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Fifteen Men, Fifteen Women, Six Children and Three Negroes, 05/15/1778 (Item 111)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Four Named Men Going to Camp, 05/18/1778 (Item 112)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Two Boys and a Negro Belonging to the Fourth Battalion, 05/19/1778 (Item 113)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Eight Men, Fourteen Women, Six Children, Four Taylors, and One Negro, 05/19/1778 (Item 114)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Four Taylors, Nine Men, Fourteen Women, Six Children, Three Boys and Two Negroes, 05/22/1778 (Item 115)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John Bennis for Eight Men and Women with List of Persons Provided for, 05/25/1778 (Item 116)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Seven Men, Fourteen Women, Eight Boys and Children, Four Taylors, and Two Negroes, 05/26/1778 (Item 117)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Eight Men, Fourteen Women, Four Taylors, Nine Boys and Children and Three Negroes, 05/29/1778 (Item 118)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Nine Men, Fifteen Women, Four Taylors, Seven Boys and Children and Two Negroes, 06/?/1778 (Item 119)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shem Cook of the Second Battalion for Twenty-eight Rations [Torn], [06/1778] (Item 120)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Chris Hillary for William Routledge, 06/02/1778-08/06/1778 (Item 121)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright to Thomas Manning, 06/02/1778 (Item 122)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Thomas Cook for One Officer, Four Sergeants, Twenty-six Privates and Eight Women, 06/04/1778 (Item 123)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White [Whiett] for James Seymour in Capt. Brossard's Company, [06/04/1778] (Item 124)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Terry Owens, 06/04/1778-06/08/1778 (Item 125)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Eight Men, Thirteen Women, Four Taylors, Five Boys and Children and Two Negroes for People Left in Town, 06/05/1778 (Item 126)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright to John Athel, 06/06/1778 (Item 127)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Fifteen Men, Twelve Women, Six Children, and Two Negroes, 06/09/1778 (Item 128)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Illegible for Catherine Tyrall, 06/10/1778-06/16/1778; Indexed #247 (Item 129)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Fourteen Men, Thirteen Women, Six Children, Two Boys, and Two Negroes, 06/12/1778 (Item 130)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Three Men and One Woman, 06/15?/1778-06/22/1778 (Item 131)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for [?] Men, Thirteen Women, Three Taylors, Eight Boys and Children and Two Negroes, 06/16/1778 (Item 132)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John Bennis for Officers and Rank and File, 06/19/1778 (Item 133)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by [Illegible] for Rum for Forty-eight Men, 06/21/1778 (Item 134)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Sixteen Men, Twenty-two Women, Six Children, Two Boys, and Four Negroes, 06/23/1778 (Item 135)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Nine Sergeants, Two Corporals, Seven Privates, Three Taylors, Nineteen Women, Seven Boys and Children and Four Negroes, 06/26/1778 (Item 136)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Phillip Lowe for Rum, 06/28/1778 (Item 137)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Fourteen Men, Eighteen Women, Three Taylors, Seven Boys and Children and Four Negroes, 06/29/1778 (Item 138)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion at Fort Tonyn Signed by [Phillip Lowe] for Rum, 07/02/1778 (Item 139)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion at Fort Tonyn Signed by [Phillip Lowe], 07/04/1778 (Item 140)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John Bennis for Twenty-eight Men, 07/20/1778 (Item 141)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Brigade Signed by Shadrack Wright for Thirty-eight Men, Nineteen Women, Three Taylors, Three Children, and Two Negroes, 07/23/1778 (Item 142)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Bernard Patty for Abraham [Illegible], 07/26/1778-08/18/1778 (Item 143)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by William Hornby for Capt. Hornby [Torn], 08/[01]/1778-08/31/1778 (Item 144)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed John Lucas to Mordecal Sheftall for Fresh Provisions "If you have got it as I have Received no Rations since my return from the Expedition", 08/03/1778; WPA_E-0129; Indexed #045 (Item 145)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Robert Ellice and John Lucas for Two Men, 08/04/1778 (Item 146)
        - Provision Return for 4th Battalion Signed by [Benjamin] Tetard Received by Benjamin Tetard, Surgeon, 08/06/1778 (Item 147)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Joseph Day for Twelve Men, Sixteen Women and Children, and One Negro, 08/07/1778 (Item 148)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Joseph Day for Sgt. White and Thomas Brown "going to Sunbury", 08/11/1778 (Item 149)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Illegible, 08/12/1778 (Item 150)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Joseph Day for Ten Men, Eleven Women, Five Children, One Child, and One Negro, 08/12/1778 (Item 151)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Bernard Patty for Matt Kinnie, 08/12/1778 (Item 152)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Regiment Signed by Bernard Patty and James [?] for Lt. Fitzpatrick and Lt. [?] and One Bowman, 08/17/1778-08/22/1778 (Item 153)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Bernard Patty and John O'Neil with Numbers of Persons Provided for, 08/19/1778-08/20/1778 (Item 154)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by George Rain and Bernard Patty for Four Named Persons, 08/21/1778-08/23/1778 (Item 155)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Edward Cowan with Numbers of Persons Provided for and Provisions, 08/21/1778-08/23/1778 (Item 156)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Bernard Patty with Numbers of Persons Provided for and Provisions, 08/24/1778-08/25/1778 (Item 157)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Bernard Patty for Thomas Manning and James Gorman, 08/25/1778 (08/23/1778-08/26/1778) (Item 158)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Matt W. Kinnie for Matt W. Kinnie, 08/26/1778 (Item 159)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Bernard Patty with Numbers of Persons Provided for and Provisions, 08/26/1778-08/27/1778 (Item 160)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by George Melvern for Eleven Men, Eleven Women, and Seven Children, 09/01/1778 (Item 161)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by George Melvern for George Melven, 09/01/1778-09/10/1778 (Item 162)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by William Hornby for Capt. Hornby, 09/01/1778-09/15/1778 (Item 163)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by George Melvern for [Eight Men], Nine Women, and Seven Children [Torn], [09]/01/1778 (Item 164)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Capt. Washington for Capt. Washington (Two returns), 09/01/1778-11/01/1778; WPA_H-0034; Indexed #020 (Item 165)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by George Melvern for Eight Men, Nine Women, and Seven Children, 09/02/1778-09/03/1778 (Item 166)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John Caswell, 09/07/1778-09/08/1778 (Item 167)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Celeron Brossard for Bernard Patty, 09/08/1778-09/22/1778 (Item 168)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by George Melvern for Eight Men, Nine Women, and Seven Children, 09/09/1778-09/10/1778 (Item 169)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Matt W. Kinnie for Matt. W. Kinnie, [and Bowman], 09/10/1778 (Item 170)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by George Melvern for Eighteen Men [Torn], [09]/10/[1778]-[09]/18/[1778] (Item 171)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by George Melvern for Ten Men, Nine Women, and Seven Children, 09/11/1778-09/13/1778 (Item 172)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White from Robert Ellice for Twenty-eight ½ Rations, 09/14/1778-09/15/1778 (Item 173)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White for Celeron Brossard, 09/15/1778 (Item 174)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White for [Eight] Men, Nine Women, and Three Children, 09/16/1778-09/17/1778 (Item 175)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Matt W. Kinnie for Matt. W. Kinnie, 09/16/1778-09/23/1778 (Item 176)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by William Hornby for William Hornby, 09/16/1778-09/30/1778 (Item 177)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White for Six Men "come round from Sunbury in a boat", 09/[17?]1778 (Item 178)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White to Mordecai Sheftall for Nathaniel Mason and "six men going in the Boat for Sunbury", 09/17/1778 (Item 179)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Celeron Brossard for Celeron Brossard and Lt. DeBorde, 09/18/1778 (Item 180)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by John White for Ten Men, Nine Women, and Three Children, 09/18/1778-09/20/1778 (Item 181)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by George Melvern for George Melven, 09/18/1778-09/30/1778 (Item 182)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by William Hornby from Robert Ellice for Nine Men, Eight Women, and Three Children, 09/21/1778-03/22/1778 (Item 183)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Celeron Brossard for Celeron Brossard, 09/21/1778-09/22/1778 (Item 184)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Celeron Brossard for Bernard Patty, 09/21/1778-09/21/1778 (Item 185)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by William Hornby for Matthew Lively on Furlough, George Keen, and John Henderson, 09/23/1778-09/27/1778 (Item 186)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by William Hornby for Eight Men, Nine, Women, and Three Children, 09/23/1778-09/24/1778 (Item 187)
        - Provision Return for the 4th Battalion Signed by Celeron Brossard for Celeron Brossard and Lt. DeBorde, 09/23/1778 (Item 188)